<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jira Automation Rules</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tools_and_scripts/jira_automation/jira_auto_release_versions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tools_and_scripts/jira_automation/jira_auto_release_versions/</guid>
      <description>This section describes a series of Jira Automation Rules that can be used to&#xA;Problem Statement:&#xD;In Jira Cloud, each project has unique Release versions. There is no concept of a &amp;ldquo;shared&amp;rdquo; version across multiple projects.&#xA;However, you can use Jira&amp;rsquo;s Automation features along with some custom fields and a designated ticket to automatically create and assign common releases across multiple projects.&#xA;Example&#xD;You might need this if your company performs regular deployments of a group of software services, and the development teams that support those services each use different Jira projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slack App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/tools_and_scripts/slack_app/slack_app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/tools_and_scripts/slack_app/slack_app/</guid>
      <description>This section describes a series of Jira Automation Rules that can be used to&#xA;Problem Statement:&#xD;In Jira Cloud, each project has unique Release versions. There is no concept of a &amp;ldquo;shared&amp;rdquo; version across multiple projects.&#xA;However, you can use Jira&amp;rsquo;s Automation features along with some custom fields and a designated ticket to automatically create and assign common releases across multiple projects.&#xA;Example&#xD;You might need this if your company performs regular deployments of a group of software services, and the development teams that support those services each use different Jira projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Guides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/technical_guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/technical_guides/</guid>
      <description>Installation Guide Installation and Configuration Guide Service Requirements Administrator Guide Installation Guide&#xD;This writing sample is a set of installation and configuration instructions for upgrading a software product for a major software release.&#xA;Installation and Configuration Guide&#xD;This writing sample is a set of installation and configuration instructions for upgrading a software product for a major software release.&#xA;Service Requirements&#xD;This writing sample is a set of software and hardware requirements necessary for implementing a given software solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes Samples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/rn_samples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/rn_samples/</guid>
      <description> Product Release Notes Hotfix Release Notes Product Release Notes&#xD;This writing sample is a set of release notes for a patch release that introduces a couple new features, information about forthcoming features, and setup (system version) requrements. This was produced with MadCap Flare, and showcases templating and conditional output for specific products and audiences.&#xA;Hotfix Release Notes&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/style_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/style_guide/</guid>
      <description>This is a generic style guide derived from the excellent Gitlab Style Guide.&#xA;Introduction&#xD;This document defines the standards for Company documentation, including grammar, formatting, word use, and more.&#xA;For style questions, create an issue or merge request with the docs team.&#xA;Introduction Why? The documentation includes all of our information The documentation includes all media types Topic types Link instead of repeating text Docs-first methodology Markdown HTML in Markdown Markdown Rules Structure Folder structure overview Work with directories and files Avoid duplication References across documents Structure in documents Writing Style Guidelines Language Trademark Capitalization Headings UI text Feature names Other terms Inclusive language Avoid gender-specific wording Avoid ableist language Culturally sensitive language Fake user information Fake URLs Fake tokens Usage list Contractions Text Emphasis Punctuation Placeholder text Keyboard commands Spaces between words Lists Ordered vs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my portfolio site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024/04/06/welcome-to-my-portfolio-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024/04/06/welcome-to-my-portfolio-site/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to introduce you to my personal portfolio website! As a technical writer with a passion for creating clear and concise documentation, this site serves as a showcase of my professional journey, skills, and accomplishments.&#xA;Built with Hugo and Hosted on GitHub Pages&#xD;I chose Hugo as the static site generator (SSG) for its speed, flexibility, and ease of use. Hugo allows me to quickly build and deploy a fast, secure, and reliable website without the need for a complex content management system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>About Personal summary and resume Daniel R. Finn&#xD;Somerville, MA • (978) 987 7694 • danfinn5@gmail.com • www.linkedin.com/in/danielrfinn&#xA;Personal Summary&#xD;I am a seasoned technical writer with over ten years of expereince documenting complex software products in dynamic and demanding environments. I have a demonstrated ability to drive strategy, lead teams, and collaborate cross-functionally to deliver high-quality documentation for multiple audiences.&#xA;Experience&#xD;Takeoff Technologies Inc., Waltham, MA&#xD;Senior Technical Writer 2020 – Present</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
