<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing Samples on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing Samples on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:06:57 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Technical Guides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/technical_guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/technical_guides/</guid>
      <description>Installation Guide Installation and Configuration Guide Service Requirements Administrator Guide Installation Guide&#xD;This writing sample is a set of installation and configuration instructions for upgrading a software product for a major software release.&#xA;Installation and Configuration Guide&#xD;This writing sample is a set of installation and configuration instructions for upgrading a software product for a major software release.&#xA;Service Requirements&#xD;This writing sample is a set of software and hardware requirements necessary for implementing a given software solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes Samples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/rn_samples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/rn_samples/</guid>
      <description> Product Release Notes Hotfix Release Notes Product Release Notes&#xD;This writing sample is a set of release notes for a patch release that introduces a couple new features, information about forthcoming features, and setup (system version) requrements. This was produced with MadCap Flare, and showcases templating and conditional output for specific products and audiences.&#xA;Hotfix Release Notes&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/style_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/writing_samples/style_guide/</guid>
      <description>This is a generic style guide derived from the excellent Gitlab Style Guide.&#xA;Introduction&#xD;This document defines the standards for Company documentation, including grammar, formatting, word use, and more.&#xA;For style questions, create an issue or merge request with the docs team.&#xA;Introduction Why? The documentation includes all of our information The documentation includes all media types Topic types Link instead of repeating text Docs-first methodology Markdown HTML in Markdown Markdown Rules Structure Folder structure overview Work with directories and files Avoid duplication References across documents Structure in documents Writing Style Guidelines Language Trademark Capitalization Headings UI text Feature names Other terms Inclusive language Avoid gender-specific wording Avoid ableist language Culturally sensitive language Fake user information Fake URLs Fake tokens Usage list Contractions Text Emphasis Punctuation Placeholder text Keyboard commands Spaces between words Lists Ordered vs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
